<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blogs</title>
	<atom:link href="https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/category/blogs/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 07:55:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/28.png</url>
	<title>Blogs</title>
	<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Social Media Optimization</title>
		<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/social-media-optimization/</link>
					<comments>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/social-media-optimization/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 07:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/?p=94</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[re you looking to grab a piece of the digital marketing pie? This guide is for you. A career in Digital marketing is a substantial decision. With or without prior [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>re you looking to grab a piece of the digital marketing pie? This guide is for you.</p>



<p>A career in Digital marketing is a substantial decision. With or without prior experience, there is always time to enter the dynamic online marketing field. You do not need to attend a college or university for a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.wscubetech.com/online-digital-marketing-course-india.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>digital marketing course</strong></a>, as many resources are available online to acquire the necessary skills.</p>



<p>That’s the beauty of this industry. You don’t need to be certified to work as a digital marketer. There are no gatekeepers.</p>



<p>If you are looking for a creative role in tech that lets you make big-picture plans, write clever copy, and even spend some days chatting with fans on Instagram, digital marketing could be your ideal career. That’s why this is an all-encompassing guide to building a career in digital marketing with no experience, one step at a time. Read it, bookmark it, live it.</p>



<p>Digital marketing promotes products, services, or brands via social media, search engines, email, websites, and mobile apps. It encompasses various techniques and tactics. This includes&nbsp;<a href="https://www.wscubetech.com/blog/latest-social-media-marketing-trends-india/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">social media marketing</a>, content marketing, Pay-Per-Click (PPC) advertising, influencer marketing, search engine optimization, email marketing, and more.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Digital marketing aspires to reach and engage with an audience through digital channels to drive conversions and sales and ultimately grow a business.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/social-media-optimization/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Email Marketing and How Does It Work? Types, Pros and Cons, Email Marketing Strategy Plan 2024</title>
		<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/what-is-email-marketing-and-how-does-it-work-types-pros-and-cons-email-marketing-strategy-plan-2024/</link>
					<comments>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/what-is-email-marketing-and-how-does-it-work-types-pros-and-cons-email-marketing-strategy-plan-2024/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 07:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/?p=91</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Despite the rise in social media platforms, email marketing is still the best-known and most effective form of digital communication. It is the most profitable form of direct marketing, generating [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite the rise in social media platforms, email marketing is still the best-known and most effective form of digital communication. It is the most profitable form of direct marketing, generating an ROI of $42 for every $1 spent.&nbsp;Some business professionals, marketers, and beginners still wonder&nbsp;<strong>what is email marketing and how does it work.&nbsp;</strong>Can it be beneficial for their business goals<strong>?</strong></p>



<p>Let’s understand the meaning of email marketing and how does email marketing work in the comprehensive write-up.</p>



<p>It is one of the top marketing strategies because it is budget-friendly and saves time. Also, when done following a plan, it can generate sales, drive traffic and maximize profits.&nbsp;</p>



<p>It is a vast discipline with plenty of&nbsp;<a href="https://www.wscubetech.com/blog/top-free-email-marketing-tools-platforms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">email marketing tools</a>&nbsp;and techniques to execute a successful campaign. And, if you’re a beginner and want to know more about email marketing, hang in tight; we’ll discuss on:</p>



<ol>
<li>Email Marketing Definition and Meaning</li>



<li>What are the advantages and disadvantages of email marketing?</li>



<li>How many types of email<strong>&nbsp;</strong>marketing are there?</li>



<li>What is the best email marketing strategy?</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/what-is-email-marketing-and-how-does-it-work-types-pros-and-cons-email-marketing-strategy-plan-2024/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Become SEO Freelancer? 2024 Guide for Beginners</title>
		<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/how-to-become-seo-freelancer-2024-guide-for-beginners/</link>
					<comments>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/how-to-become-seo-freelancer-2024-guide-for-beginners/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 07:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/?p=87</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We are living in a digital era, where every click holds the potential to shape online destinies. In this era, Search Engine Optimization (SEO) stands as the silent architect behind [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are living in a digital era, where every click holds the potential to shape online destinies. In this era, Search Engine Optimization (<a href="https://www.wscubetech.com/blog/digital-marketing/search-engine-optimization/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">SEO</a>) stands as the silent architect behind the scenes. As businesses look to boost their online presence, the demand for skilled SEO professionals has grown very high.</p>



<p>For those looking to start their digital entrepreneurship journey, SEO freelancing emerges as an enticing route. If you’ve ever wondered how to become an SEO freelancer or begin a career in it, you’re in the right place.</p>



<p>In this comprehensive SEO freelancing guide, let’s understand all the essentials of SEO freelancing, from search algorithms, keywords, and client interactions to becoming a highly-paid professional.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Whether you’re a recent graduate, a career switcher, or a seasoned marketer looking to diversify, this guide aims to equip you with the knowledge, skills, and strategies needed to flourish in the filed of SEO freelancing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/how-to-become-seo-freelancer-2024-guide-for-beginners/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meesho</title>
		<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/meesho/</link>
					<comments>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/meesho/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 06:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/?p=45</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Meesho  fashion near technologies private Ltd company.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fashnear Technologies Private Limited was established by <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IIT_Delhi">I</a>graduates Vidit Aatrey and Sanjeev Barnwal in July, 2015<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-:2-6">[</a></sup>as an on-demand delivery service like but for fashion products from local shops. The startup failed. In 2016, the founders came up with the idea of re-establishing the platform as Meesho, one that would enable country-wide shipping for resellers with the use of social media sites as tools for marketing.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-7">[7]</a></sup><sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-:0-3">[3]</a></sup></p>



<p>Meesho had 209,000 users and 1.2 million orders per month in February 2019 and 563,000 users and 3.1 million orders per month in March 2020.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-8">[8]</a></sup> It saw big growth during 2021 and 2022.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-9">[9]</a></sup> Meesho&#8217;s monthly transacting user count rose 26 times during 2020–2022. Globally, Meesho was among the top most downloaded apps in 2021.In 2022, Meesho had about 120 million monthly users and about 910 million orders were made through the platform. It soon became one of India&#8217;s fastest growing e-commerce platforms.Its (GMV) increased ninefold in two years<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meesho#cite_note-:3-11">[</a></sup>and was at about $5 billion in 2022 (for comparison, &#8216;s GMV stood at $23 billion).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex">
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="1600" height="1200" data-id="47" src="https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/13.png" alt="" class="wp-image-47"/></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="768" height="576" data-id="48" src="https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/14.png" alt="" class="wp-image-48"/></figure>
</figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/meesho/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 04:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://yusufvinfo.github.io/blog/2023/12/23/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
